regalbeloit.com 2019-08-09

# Privacy | Regal Beloit

**REGAL BELOIT GLOBAL PRIVACY POLICY**

Regal Beloit Group, which includes Regal Beloit Corporation and its subsidiaries, divisions and  all affiliates (collectively Regal) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our personal information gathering practices in connection with personal information we receive both online (through our websites and applications - please note that reference to “website” in this privacy policy should be read to include “applications” ) and offline (e.g. via the phone, conferences and other correspondence).

This Privacy Policy also applies to your personal information that is processed by our brands and through our brands’ websites and applications. A list of these can be found below:

Brand | Website  
---|---  
Browning | http://www.regalpts.com  
Cemp | http://www.cemp-international.it  
Durst | http://www.regalpts.com  
Elco | http://www.elco-spa.com  
Fasco | http://www.fasco.com  
Foote-Jones | http://www.regalpts.com  
Grove Gear | http://www.grovegear.com  
Hub-City | http://www.hubcityinc.com  
Jaure | http://www.regalpts.com  
Kop-Flex | http://www.regalpts.com  
Marathon Generators | https://www.marathongenerators.com  
Marathon Special Products | http://www.marathonsp.com  
Thompson Power Systems | https://www.thomsonps.com  
McGill | http://www.regalpts.com  
Milwaukee Gear | http://www.regalpts.com  
Morrill | http://www.morrillmotors.com  
Morse | http://www.regalpts.com  
Rollway | http://www.regalpts.com  
Rotor | https://www.rotor.nl  
Sealmaster | http://www.regalpts.com  
System Plast | http://www.regalpts.com  
Genteq | https://www.genteqmotors.com  
Nicotra-Gebhardt | http://www.nicotra-gebhardt.com  
  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Regal at the e-mail address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

Please note that where you are a national within the European Economic Area (EEA),we are required to provide you with additional information about our processing activities. As well as this Global Privacy Policy, please refer to the European Appendix for this additional information. 

**1.WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?  **

We may collect and process the following personal information about you:

 **Information about you.** This may include information such as your name, address and contact details (business and/or personal), “business card information”, the Regal products and brands you are interested in and your marketing preferences, Regal events which you have attended or signed up to and any information you provide to us voluntarily such as through forms you fill in, when you attend our conferences, or when you contact customer support services.

**Details of your transactions and payment details.** Your order details and payment details used to purchase our products and services such as credit or debit card number and expiry date, account information relating to other payment services and billing information,

**Credit and Anti-Fraud information.** Information relating to your financial situation, your creditworthiness or any criminal or fraudulent activities provided to us by you or third parties including information which establishes your identity, such as driving licenses, passports and utility bills; information about transactions, credit ratings from credit reference agencies; fraud, offences, suspicious transactions, politically exposed person and sanctions lists where your details are included.

**Our interactions with you.**   We may keep a record of any interactions and correspondence between us such as calls made to our customer support services, any interactions you have with our representatives and any interactions with us or posts that refer to us on social media. 

**Survey information.** We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes.  In such circumstances we shall collect the information provided in the completed survey.

Your use of the website, including your IP Address. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using. Regal collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic of our websites and to maintain and improve the website.

Use of Cookies and other tracking technologies. Cookies are small bits of information that some websites (including our websites) transfer to an individual's hard drive for various purposes. Regal uses cookies and other tracking technologies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on our websites, to make improvements based on the data we collect and to enhance and personalize your experience. Regal never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry, especially at websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of our websites. Our website advertisers and other partners may also use cookies in connection with the services and websites to which our websites link. We do not control these cookies.

Please note that where you are a national within the European Economic Area (EEA), we are required to provide you with additional information about our use of cookies. As well as this document, please refer to our Cookies Policy for this additional information.

 **2.WHO IS COLLECTING THIS PERSONAL INFORMATION?** Regal collects the information described above via our websites and other offline channels. In the case of third party features such as advertising, co-branded areas or links to other websites, such third parties may also collect information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. Regal is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties..

**3.USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.   **

Regal may use your personal information in the following ways: 

(a) To provide our products and services to you. For example, to enable you to explore products that you may purchase, supply or distribute or to use services (e.g. on our websites), to collect payment, to set up an account for you and to ensure that such  account is secure, and to enable us to identify you as a user of our products and services.

(b) To communicate effectively with you and conduct our business. For example. providing you with administrative emails and corresponding with you when you register to receive information or provide any correspondence, such as posting a comment on  our social media channels and to inform you of changes. We will also communicate with you in relation to enquiries you make about employment opportunities.

(c) For research and development purposes. For example when you participate in a survey, or we gather demographic information about our user base and analyze trends about our users based on information they provide and their interactions with us.

(d) To provide you with marketing material. For example to promote our services or to send you promotional materials, newsletters, upgrades and special offers about our products and services by email and through social media. We may also use your personal information to analyze our customers’ preferences and market trends and derive insights, which we may use to tailor the types of products and offers that we present to you  This may involve us combining personal information that we hold about your use of our services with information that we have collected about your web usage. Where required by law, we will ask for your consent at the time we collect your data to conduct any of these types of marketing.  We will provide an option to unsubscribe or opt-out of further communication on any electronic marketing communication sent to you. We also use advertising services and products provided by third party service providers (such as marketing agencies and social media platforms) for marketing and promotional purposes, which may involve us sharing  personal information we hold about you with them.

(e) To monitor certain activities. For example users’ movements around the website, such as the date and time of your visit, details of the information collected through cookies and other tracking methodologies, including but not limited to your IP address, domain name, browser type, operating system and the solutions and information for which you searched. We also monitor activities as part of our compliance procedures and to combat fraud.

(f) To administer our website. Including to ensure that  the content is relevant and presented to you in the most effective manner for you and to ensure compliance with our Website Terms and Conditions.

(g) To comply with our legal obligations. To comply with our regulatory requirements or dialogue with regulators as applicable which may include disclosing your personal information to third parties, the court service and/or regulators or law enforcement agencies  in  connection  with  enquiries, proceedings or investigations by such parties anywhere in the world or where compelled to do so.  Where permitted, we will direct any such request to you or notify you before responding unless to do so would prejudice the prevention or detection of a crime.  

(h) In connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of our business, such as if we undergo a reorganization, where we may need to transfer some or all of your Personal information to a third party or its advisors as part of any due diligence process for the purpose of analysing the proposed sale or reorganization or after the sale or reorganization for the same purposes as set out in this Privacy Policy. 

**4.WITH WHOM THE PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED.** In addition to any disclosees specified in section 3 above, we may disclose personal information for the purposes we explain in this Privacy Policy to service providers, contractors, agents, advisors (e.g.  legal, financial, business or other advisors) and affiliates of Regal that perform activities on our behalf, as well as other members of the Regal group . Except as described in section 3 and this section 4, Regal will not knowingly disclose or authorize the disclosure of your personal information  to any third party unless (1) we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Website Terms and Conditions or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Regal’s rights or property, other website users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities or (2) we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

**5.CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YEARS**. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Regal will not knowingly collect personal information from a child under the age of 13 without a parent’s or guardian’s prior consent.

**6.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES.** While you are using the Website, you may be linked or directed to other third party websites outside the Website that are beyond Regal’s control. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of Regal. Regal is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party websites before providing personally identifiable information.

**7.SECURITY PROCEDURES WE USE.** We are very concerned with the security of your personal information and take great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission (both over the Internet or otherwise) can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide to us.

Once we receive your information, we take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your data on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect. We use a combination of technological and policy methods to protect this data.

**8.CHANGES IN THESE TERMS.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and will post notices on the Website at the time of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions or concerns regarding RBC's Website Use Privacy Policy, please e-mail Regal at data.protection@regalbeloit.com. 

 **EUROPEAN APPENDIX**

This European Appendix forms part of the Global Privacy Policy and applies if you are based in the EEA during your interactions with us (other than where you are in the EEA solely for travel purposes). This European Appendix sets out the additional information that we are required to provide to you under European data protection laws, including information about the additional rights you may have under European data protection laws. This European Appendix should be read alongside the Global Privacy Policy and terms used in this European Appendix have the meaning given in the Global Privacy Policy.

**1\. Why we collect your personal information, and who we disclose it to?**

When we use your personal information, we take care to ensure that it is used in an appropriate way. Use of personal information (and special categories of personal information) under European data protection law must be based on one of a number of legal grounds and we are required to set out the grounds in respect of each use in the Global Privacy Policy. In the table below, we have set out the relevant grounds that apply to each purpose mentioned in section 3 of the Global Privacy Policy. You can find an explanation of each of the grounds relied on at section 2 of this European Appendix:

Purposes of the data processing | Use bases  
---|---  
**3(a) To provide our products and services to you** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to allow us to perform our obligations and provide services to you)

**3(b) To communicate effectively with you and conduct our business** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to allow us to correspond with you in connection with our services)

**3(c) For research and development purposes** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to allow us to maintain and improve the quality of our services and products)

**3(d) To provide you with marketing materials** | 

  * legitimate interests (to market our products and services)
  * consent (in relation to certain electronic marketing where required by law)(which can be withdrawn at any time)

**3(e) To monitor certain activities** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to ensure the quality and legality of our services)
  * legal obligations

For special categories of personal information:

  * legal claims
  * legitimate interests (to ensure the quality and legality of our services)
  * legal obligations

**3(f) To administer our website** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to allow us to provide you with the content and services on our websites)

**3(g) To comply with our legal obligations** | 

  * legal obligation
  * legitimate interests (to cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory authorities)
  * legal claims

For special categories of personal information:

  * legal claims
  * substantial public interest (to prevent or detect crime or fraud)

**3(h) In connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of our business** | 

  * legitimate interests (in order to allow us to change our business)

**3(g) To comply with our legal obligations** | 

  * contract performance
  * legitimate interests (to allow us to provide you with the content and services on our websites)

**2\. Legal grounds for use of personal information**

2.1 The legal grounds for our use of Personal Data are as follows:

(a) Consent: where you have consented to our use of your personal information. You may withdraw your consent to the use of your personal information by contacting us as set out at section 6 of this European Appendix;   
(b) Contract performance: where we are required to collect and handle your personal information in order to provide you with the services that we have contractually agreed to provide to you.   
(c) Legal obligation: where we need to use your personal information to comply with our legal obligations; and   
(d) Legitimate interests: where we have a legitimate interest in using your personal information. We will only rely on this legal ground if we consider that our interest in using your personal information for the relevant purpose is not outweighed by any interests that you may have, or any prejudice that you may suffer, from the relevant use of your personal information.   
The legal grounds for our use of the special categories of personal information:   
(a) Legal claims: where your personal information is necessary for us to establish, exercise of defend any legal claims; and   
(b) Substantial public interest: where we need to process your personal information for reasons of substantial public interest set out in EU law or the laws of the member state in which you are based. 

**3\. Export outside the EEA**

3.1 Your personal information will be accessed by staff or suppliers, transferred, and/or stored outside the EEA, including to the US and other countries which have a lower level of data protection than under EU DP law.   
3.2 We must comply with specific rules when we transfer personal information from inside the EEA to outside the EEA. When we do this, we will use appropriate safeguards to protect any personal information being transferred.   
3.3 Certain countries outside the EEA have been approved by the European Commission as providing essentially equivalent protections to EEA data protection laws (see the full list here http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/international-transfers/adequacy/index_en.htm) and therefore no additional safeguards are required to transfer personal information to recipients in these countries.  For other countries outside the EEA, we will transfer your personal information subject to European Commission-approved contractual terms that impose different data protection obligations directly on the recipient unless we are permitted under EU data protection law to make such transfers without such formalities.   
3.4 Please contact us as set out in section 6 of this European  Appendix if you would like to see a copy of the specific safeguards we apply to the export of your personal information. 

**4\. Retention periods**

Our retention periods for personal information are based on business needs and legal requirements. We will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active and otherwise as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which it was collected and any other permitted linked purpose. Where personal information is no longer needed, we either irreversibly anonymize the data (in which case we may further retain and use the anonymized data) or securely destroy the data. 

**5\. Your rights**

5.1 Under certain conditions, you may have the right under EU data protection law to ask us to:   
(a)\provide you with further details on how we use and process your personal information;   
(b) provide you with a copy of your personal information that we hold;   
(c) update any inaccuracies in the personal information we hold;   
(d) delete personal information we no longer have grounds to process;   
(e) to ask us to transmit the personal information you have provided to us and we still hold about you to a third party electronically; and   
(f) restrict how we process your personal information whilst we consider an inquiry you have raised.   
5.2 In addition, under certain conditions, you have the right to:  
(a) where processing is based on consent, withdraw the consent;   
(b) object to any processing of personal information that we process on the “legitimate interests” or “public interests” grounds, unless our reasons for the underlying processing outweighs your interests, rights and freedoms; and   
(c) object to direct marketing (including any profiling for such purposes) at any time   
5.3 You can exercise these rights by contacting us as per section 6 of this European Appendix.   
5.4 These rights are subject to certain exemptions to safeguard the public interest (e.g. the prevention or detection of crime) and our interests (e.g. the maintenance of legal privilege). We will respond to most requests within one month.   
5.5 If we are unable to resolve an inquiry or a complaint, you have the right to contact the data protection regulator in the EEA country in which you are based. A list of the data protection regulators and their contact details can be found at http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080. 

**6\. Contact details**

6.1 Depending on where you are located, the “data controller” of your personal information processed by us under this Privacy Policy will be different. Please see below for a list of which group companies will be data controllers in which countries.   
6.2 Please contact data.protection@regalbeloit.com if you have any questions or would like to exercise any of your rights under EU data protection law. 

Name | Registered Address | Country of Establishments | Registration Number  
---|---|---|---  
Regal Beloit Belgium NV | Heiveldekens 16 Kontich, Antwerpen, Belgium 2550 | Belgium | BE 0416.998.941  
Elco BG Property EOOD | 104 Akad Ivan Geshov Boulvd Sofia Bulgaria | Bulgaria | 175158455  
Regal Beloit France SAS | 14 Rue des Cours, Neuves za de la Peupleraie, Pontcarre | France | 33295032800028  
Regal Beloit GmbH | Postfach 10 55 53 Dusseldorf 40046 | Germany | HRB13906  
Cemp International GmbH | Dr Atzinger Strasse 5 Passau D-94036 | Germany | DE8136347793  
System Plast GmbH | Gewerbering Strasse 14 Dohna 01809 | Germany | 210/118/03862  
Cemp Srl | Via Piemonte 16 Senago 20030 | Italy | IT05933500968  
Elco E-Trade S.r.l. | Via del Brugo No 5 Legnano Milan 20025 | Italy | 02060700160  
System Plast S.R.L. | Via G Marconi 1 Inzago Milan 20065 | Italy | 646900167  
RBC Foreign Manufacturing B.V. | Hoogoorddreef 15, 1101 BA Amsterdam | The Netherlands | 343.292.37  
Rotor B.V. | Mors 1-5, 7151 MX, Eibergen | The Netherlands | 08030665  
Regal Beloit România SRL | 21 Garii Street, Building D, 2nd Floor, space 1 Cluj-Napoca, Cluj County | Romania | J12/2369/06.08.2015  
Regal Beloit Slovakia, s.r.o. | Piest’anska 1202 915 01 Nove Mesto mad Vahom | Slovakia | 48 029 360  
Regal Beloit Spain S.A. | Ernio Bidea, S/N Zizurkil (Gipuzkoa) 20159 | Spain | A20034278  
Opperman Mastergear Ltd. (closed) | Marshall Way, Heapham Road Industrial Estate, Gainsborough, Lincolnshire DN21 1XU | United Kingdom | 02618553  
Regal Beloit UK Ltd | 30 Harborough Road, Northampton NN2 7AZ | United Kingdom | 4595019  
Regal Manufacturing Limited | One, New Change, London EC4M 9AF | United Kingdom | 00516559  
Rotor (UK) Limited | 16 Everitt Close Denington Industrial EstateWellingborough NN8 2QF | United Kingdom | 5098331  
System Plast Limited | Highdown House, 11 Highdown Road, Leamington Spa, Warwickshire CV31 1XT  | United Kingdom | 3211982  
  
**REGAL BELOIT COOKIE POLICY**

**Consent**

By using this website www.regalbeloit.com (the "Website") you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with this Cookies Policy. You will have seen a pop up to this effect on your first visit to this website; although it will not usually appear on subsequent visits you may withdraw your consent at any time by following the instructions below.

**Disabling cookies**

If you do not agree to the use of these cookies please disable them by following the instructions for your browser set out here: http://allaboutcookies.org. Please note that some of the services will not function so well if cookies are disabled.

Where the organization setting the cookie provides an automated disabling tool in respect of its cookie(s) we list the name of that organization, the category of cookies it sets together with a link to its automated disabling tool. In all other cases, we list the names of the cookies themselves and their source at the date of this Cookies policy so that you can easily identify and disable them if you want through your browser controls. 

Some browsers make is possible for you to signal that you do not want your internet browsing activity to be tracked. Disabling tracking may interfere with some uses of the Website and the services provided on the Website. 

After your initial visit to the Website we may change the cookies we use. This cookies policy will always allow you to know who is placing cookies, for what purpose and give you the means to disable them so you should check it from time to time.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating web domain on your subsequent visits to that domain. Most web pages contain elements from multiple web domains so when you visit the Website, your browser may receive cookies from several sources.

Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device. Cookies allow you to navigate between pages efficiently, remember preferences and generally improve the user experience. They can also be used to tailor advertising to your interests through tracking your browsing across websites.

Session cookies are deleted automatically when you close your browser and persistent cookies remain on your device after the browser is closed (for example to remember your user preferences when you return to the site). 

**What types of cookies does www.regalbeloit.com use? **

We describe the categories of cookies www.regalbeloit.com and its affiliates and its contractors use below. 

**A. Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for (such as navigating between pages) cannot be provided. 

This Website currently uses the following strictly necessary cookies:

Cookie Name | Source | Purpose | Further Information  
---|---|---|---  
ASP.NET_SessionId | Microsoft | General purpose platform session cookie, used by sites written with Microsoft .NET based technologies. Usually used to maintain an anonymized user session by the server. | Session Cookie  
  
**B. Performance Cookies**

We make use of analytic cookies to analyze how our visitors use our Website and to monitor Website performance. This allows us to provide a high quality experience by customizing our offering and quickly identifying and fixing any issues that arise. For example, we might use performance cookies to keep track of which pages are most popular, which method of linking between pages is most effective, and to determine why some pages are receiving error messages. We might also use these cookies to highlight articles or site services that we think will be of interest to you based on your usage of the website. The information collected by these cookies is not associated with your personal information by us or by our contractors.

The Website currently uses the following analytic cookies [from Google Analytics]

Cookie Name | Source | Purpose | Further Information  
---|---|---|---  
_ceg.s | Crazy Egg | This cookie name is associated with software provided by Crazy Egg Inc., a USA based company providing web analytics that tracks how visitors interact with pages on a site. | Persistent cookie. Expires after 3 Months.  
_ceg.u | Crazy Egg | This cookie name is associated with software provided by Crazy Egg Inc., a USA based company providing web analytics that tracks how visitors interact with pages on a site. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance. Track visitors on the site.  | Persistent cookie. Expires after 3 Months.  
_ceir | Crazy Egg | This cookie name is associated with software provided by Crazy Egg Inc., a USA based company providing web analytics that tracks how visitors interact with pages on a site. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance Track whether a visitor has visited the site before. | Persistent cookie. Expires after 5 Years.  
_cfduid | Cloud Flare | Default thumbnail images can be inserted via the service by placehold.it. These images are delivered via a Content Delivery Network (CDN) called CloudFlare. This simply means, that the images are delivered from a cache, which makes them quicker to retrieve. This cookie is used to ensure a secure connection and is necessary for this functionality to work. No sensitive data is saved. Cookie associated with sites using CloudFlare, used to speed up page load times. According to CloudFlare it is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. It does not contain any user identification information. The main purpose of this cookie is: Strictly Necessary | Persistent cookie. Expires after 5 Years.  
_ga | Google Analytics | This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics - which is a significant update to Google's more commonly used analytics service. This cookie is used to distinguish unique users by assigning a randomly generated number as a client identifier. It is included in each page request in a site and used to calculate visitor, session and campaign data for the sites analytics reports. By default it is set to expire after 2 years, although this is customizable by website owners. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance. | Persistent cookie. Expires after 2 Years.  
_gat | Google Analytics | This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics, according to documentation it is used to throttle the request rate - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites. It expires after 10 minutes. | Persistent cookie. Expires after 10 minutes.  
_gid | Google Analytics | This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics. It appears to store and update a unique value for each page visited. | Persistent cookie. Expires after 1 day.  
_hssc | HubSpot | This cookie name is associated with websites built on the HubSpot platform. It is reported by them as being used for website analytics. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance | Persistent cookie. Expires after 30 min.  
_hssrc | HubSpot | This cookie name is associated with websites built on the HubSpot platform. It is reported by them as being used for website analytics. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance | Session Cookie  
_hstc | HubSpot | This cookie name is associated with websites built on the HubSpot platform. It is reported by them as being used for website analytics. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance | Persistent cookie. Expires after 2 Years.  
SC_ANALYTICS_GLOBAL_COOKIE | Sitecore Content Management | This cookie name is associated with the Sitecore Content Management System as is used for web analytics to identify repeat visits by unique users. The main purpose of this cookie is: Performance | Persistent cookie. Expires in 10 Years.  
  
**C. Website Functionality Cookies**

We make use of cookies to provide you with certain functionality. For example, to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in), or to recognize the platform from which you access the site, and to provide enhanced and more personal features. These cookies are not used to track your browsing on other sites.

This Website uses the following functional cookies:

Cookie Name | Source | Purpose | Further Information  
---|---|---|---  
hubspotutk | HubSpot  | This cookie is used for to keep track of a visitor's identity. This cookie is passed to HubSpot on form submission and used when de-duplicating contacts. HubSpot report that its purpose is user authentication. As a persistent rather than a session cookie it cannot be classified as Strictly Necessary. The main purpose of this cookie is: Functionality | Persistent cookie. Expires in 10 Years.  
  
To opt-out of Hubspot marketing tool please use this link: https://knowledge.hubspot.com/getting-started-with-hubspot-v2/how-to-import-an-opt-out-list-into-your-account

**D. Advertising Cookies**

Advertising cookies (or targeting cookies) collect information about the browsing habits associated with your device and are used to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used by services provided by third parties on this Website, such as ‘Like’ or ‘Share’ buttons in addition to providing the requested functionality. Third parties provide these services in return for recognizing that you (or more accurately your device has) have visited a certain website. These third parties put down advertising cookies both when you visit our Website and when you use their services and navigate away from our Website. Their privacy practices are set out below: 

  * AddThis (the service that runs some of our social sharing buttons): https://www.addthis.com/privacy
  * YouTube video player cookie policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en (Google's standard terms).
  * Facebook's data use policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
  * Twitter's privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy
  * LinkedIn’s cookie policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy

In addition to the cookies set by third parties set out above, the following other cookies are also used: 

Cookie Name | Source | Purpose | Further Information  
---|---|---|---  
bbbbbbbbbbbbbbb (/OA_MEDIA/css/, /OA_HTML/, /ebizurm/, /Suppliers/, /api/Sitecore/Common/, /Brands/LEESON/Technical-Information/, /assets/Regal/fonts/, /Suppliers/Regal-Policies/)  | elitelink.regalbeloit.com | This cookie is for secured connection (session authorization cookie). | Session cookie  
iprod |  |  | Session cookie  
site24x7rumID |  | This cookie is used to enhance the performance and functionality of the website. | Persistent cookie. Expires at the end of the current month.  
_op_aixPageId |  |  | Session cookie  
  
**E. HTML email web beacons**

Our emails may contain a single, campaign-unique “web beacon pixel” to tell us whether our emails are opened and verify any clicks through to links within the email. We may use this information for purposes including determining which of our emails are more interesting to you, to query whether users who do not open our emails wish to continue receiving them. The pixel will be deleted when you delete the email. If you do not wish the pixel to be downloaded to your device, you should select to receive emails from us in plain text rather than HTML. 

**F. Use of IP addresses and web logs**

We may also use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Website and to improve the service we offer to you. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on the internet. Your IP address might also be used to gather broad demographic information.

We may perform IP lookups to determine which domain you are coming from (e.g. google.com) to more accurately gauge our users’ demographics.

**Cookies policy does not cover third party websites**

Please note that this cookies policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the privacy practices of third party websites which may be linked to this Website.

**Changes to the Cookies Policy**

We may update this cookies policy and we would encourage you to review the policy from time to time to stay informed of how we are using cookies. This cookies policy was last updated on 5/24/2018.
